acorninfluence.com 2019-07-20

# Privacy Policy | Acorn | The Influence Company

PRIVACY POLICY 

Acorn Influence, LLC (“Acorn”, “Company” or “We”) understands the importance of privacy and accordingly, treats all information we receive in a responsible manner through compliance with this policy (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Acorn collects, uses, and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User“ or “You”) of our website (http://www.acorninfluence.com) (the “Website”) and our platform and its services found thereon (the “Platform”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Website, the Platform and any email, text and other communications between You and Acorn. Please review this Privacy Policy before accessing and using our Website and the Platform.   
By accessing and using the Website and the Platform, or by otherwise providing us with Your Personal Information (as defined below), You acknowledge that You understand our Privacy Policy and expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of Your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or the Platform. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time (see “Modification of This Privacy Policy”). Your continued use of this Website or Platform after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please periodically check the Privacy Policy for updates. 

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US 

We collect several types of information from and about Users of our Website and the Platform, including the following information: 

Personal Information 

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact You personally, including, but not limited to, User’s name, address, email address, phone number or demographic information (“Personal Information” or “personally identifiable information”). Acorn may collect Personal Information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users access or use our Website or the Platform, register with Acorn, fill out a form, respond to a survey, correspond with Acorn, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Website or through our Platform. If You elect to link Your account with a social media site, Your User information and other content for that social media account may also be collected. It is always Your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information. If You choose not to provide requested Personal Information, You may not be able to participate in certain activities or use certain features of the Website or the Platform. 

Technical Information 

We may also collect and use technical data and related information, such as information about Your device, system and application software, peripherals and other data related to Your interactions with the Platform (“Technical Information”). We may automatically collect Technical Information through cookies, flash cookies, web beacons or clear pixels and log files. The information we collect from these technologies may include, but is not limited to, Your browser or device type, IP address or other numeric codes used to identify a computer or mobile device, operating system, internet service provider, the referring web page, the time, frequency and duration of use, and the page You request. Acorn does not consider this information to be personally identifiable information. 

· Cookies: A cookie is a small data file placed on the hard drive of a User’s computer. Most browsers now automatically accept cookies by default, but they can also be set so that all or some cookies are rejected automatically or accepted or rejected on a case-by-case basis at the User’s option. If User does not wish to have cookies placed on User’s computer or wishes to be notified when they are placed, User may set User’s browser to reject cookies or notify User of their use. If a User has chosen to disable cookies on his or her browser, some of the functionality of the Website or Platform may be lost. Certain services provided by Acorn require that cookies be enabled in a User’s browser and cannot be used when cookies are disabled. 

· Flash Cookies (or Local Shared Objects or “LSOs”): Certain features of our Website and Platform may use Flash cookies to collect and store information about Your settings, preferences, usage, and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are data files similar to cookies, except that they can store more complex data. 

· Web beacons or clear pixels: Web beacons are small graphic images on a web page or in an email that can be used for such things as recording the pages and advertisements that Users select, or tracking the performance of email marketing campaigns. 

· Log Files: Log files are records of activity created by the computer that delivers the webpages requested by the User’s browser. For example, log files may record search terms or the link clicked to bring a User to a webpage. Log files also may record information about a User’s browser, such as Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, and pages viewed. Acorn does not attribute the website demands stored in the log file to specific individual Users. 

· Device information: We may collect information about the mobile device or computer used to access the Website or Platform, including without limitation the hardware model, operating system and version, browser type, unique device identifies and mobile network information. 

· Analytics tools: We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traﬃc and usage trends for the Website and the Platform. These tools collect information sent by Your browser or mobile device, including, without limitation, information such as how often Users visit this site, what pages Users visit when they do so, and what other sites Users used prior to coming to this site. We use this information to analyze, maintain and improve the Website and Platform. 

Third Party Information 

We may also collect information about You from third parties and from publicly available sources. For example, we may receive information about You through social media APIs or otherwise (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest and others). The data we receive is dependent upon Your privacy settings with the social network. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust Your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Website or Platform. 

INFORMATION YOU VOLUNTARILY DISCLOSE PUBLICLY 

Certain features of the Platform are designed to publicly display or publish information that You choose to provide to other Users of the Platform or to other third parties. Public information will include the User’s public profile and contain first name, last name, photo, bio, gender and country. The details a User provides here will be visible to registered advertisers and agencies to the Platform. 

Within the Platform, Acorn also oﬀers Influencers the opportunity to present information about their audience to prospective advertisers and agencies. Acorn displays the profile of the audience that was provided by the Influencer within the Platform. The audience profile shows the URL address, blog name, audience description, number of members, member gender, member age, member location, categories and policies. These are visible to any advertiser and agency registered to the Platform. 

USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US 

Acorn may use information we collect about You or that You provide to us, including any Personal Information, for the following purposes: (1) to operate, maintain and improve our Website and Platform; (2) to provide You with information, products or services that You request from us; (3) to process Your registration with the Website or Platform; (4) to communicate with You regarding campaigns, information, Your account, features, products, services, or oﬀers that we believe may be of interest to You; (5) to respond to Your questions or other requests; (6) to provide software updates, product support, product enhancements and other services to You related to the Website or Platform; (7) to process any payments or changes to Your account information; (8) to conduct user surveys; (9) to understand how our Users use the services and resources provided on our Website and Platform; (10) to contact You regarding a sweepstakes, contest or promotion in which You have participated; (11) for internal business purposes; and (12) for any other purposes disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time You provide Your information. 

SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD-PARTIES 

We do not rent, sell, share or otherwise disclose Your Personal Information to third parties or non-aﬃliated companies without Your consent, except in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including in the following circumstances: (i) to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us, (ii) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities on or through the Website or Platform such as fraud, identity theft, violations of Terms of Use, or infringement of intellectual property rights; (iii) in connection with a sale, purchase, merger, joint venture, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of us; (iv) when we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of it or other persons; or (v) as otherwise required or permitted by law. 

We may share Personal Information with (i) third-party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, which may include hosting services, or providing analytics services; [(ii) with third parties who advertise their products and services on the Website or other third -parties who conducts contests or sweepstakes or who may otherwise wish to send You information about their products and services. For example, Acorn may offer a discount or contest in conjunction with a co-sponsor that may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to a User. In such a case, a User’s Personal Information may be shared with the co-sponsor and their use of such User’s Personal Information will be governed by their privacy policy.] 

We may also use and share aggregated, non-personal information with third-parties, such as demographic information; the number of users who searched for a particular term or clicked on a particular advertisement; to better understand how Users engage with the content we are involved with, and to assess, improve, and quantify the response to such content. As stated earlier, such aggregated, non-personal information does not identify you individually. 

Additionally, Your information may be shared with other Users of the Platform, as needed to provide You our services under the Platform. For example, when an Advertiser creates or sends a message, the Advertiser’s first name, last name and company will be visible to selected Influencers who respond to the campaign. When an Influencer receives a message from an Advertiser and accepts the campaign, their blog name and link, URL, first name, last name and social media accounts will be visible to Advertiser. 

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES FOR YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

When You sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask You to provide Personal Information. If we wish use this information in a manner diﬀerent than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for Your consent prior to such use. If we propose to use Personal Information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific privacy notices, we will oﬀer You an eﬀective way to opt out of the use of Personal Information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary privacy notices, unless we have obtained Your prior consent. 

With respect to any Personal Information provided by User to Acorn, User shall have the rights to access, correct, delete and object to its Personal Information. Such rights may be exercised by notice in writing sent to Acorn’s registered address (as shown at the end of this Privacy Policy) or by e-mail sent to info@acorninfluence.com. Moreover, the User may unsubscribe to commercial communications received from Acorn by sending a request to info@acorninfluence.com. User can edit User’s account information at any time and/or request their User account to be deleted at any time by contacting info@acorninfluence.com; however, please note that User’s identification, billing and contact information may remain in Acorn’s records for some period after the deletion. 

THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES 

This Privacy Policy applies to Acorn’s Website and Platform only. The Website and Platform may contain links to websites and services of various third-parties, including our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third-parties, each of which has its own separate privacy and data collection practices. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these third-party websites or their content, products, services, privacy policies or data collection practices. These linked sites are for Your convenience and You access such third-party websites or content at Your own risk. 

PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We recognize the trust that our customers put in us to protect their Personal Information. We take that responsibility seriously and maintain reasonable and appropriate measures and safeguards to help protect User’s Personal Information. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect User’s Personal Information, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee or promise that such information will remain secure at all times. 

CHILDREN AND PRIVACY  

Our Website and Platform are not intended for children and we will not request personally identifiable information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, unless we have obtained verifiable parental consent from a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If You believe that we may have collected information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us at info@acorninfluence.com and we will remove the information. 

If you are a California resident and between the ages of thirteen (13) and eighteen (18), and have registered as a User, you may request the removal of Your content or information, by editing your account information or by contacting us at info@acorninfluence.com. Please note,

however, that removal of Your content or information from our Website or Platform does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, particularly if the content or information you posted has been copied and/or reposted by a third party. 

NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS 

Pursuant to the California Civil Code Sections 1798.83, Users who are California residents may request us to provide to them once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we disclosed their personal data (if any) for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of data disclosed to those third parties. California residents may contact us to make this request by email at [Acorn Email Address] or by mail to Acorn Influence, LLC, 1011 SW A Street, Suite 209, Bentonville, AR 72712.  

INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS 

Your information collected through the Website and Platform may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Acorn or its subsidiaries, aﬃliates or service providers maintain facilities. If You are located in the European Union or other regions with law governing data collection and use that may diﬀer from United States law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as Your jurisdiction, and You consent to the transfer of information to the United States or any other country in which Acorn or its subsidiaries, aﬃliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about You as described in this Privacy Policy.] 

MODIFICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

Acorn may update this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time in its sole discretion. When we do, we will update the date at the bottom of this page. User agrees that such modification shall be eﬀective upon posting on the Website and User will be bound to any modifications when User uses the Platform after such modification is posted. It is thus important for Users to frequently check this page to ensure that Users stay informed of any updates to our Privacy Policy. Should a User not agree with the changes to the Privacy Policy, User’s sole remedy shall be to close User’s account and to cease using the Website and Platform. 

CONTACT US 

If User has any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Acorn Influence, LLC  
1011 SW A Street, Suite 209  
Bentonville, AR 72712  
Email: info@acorninfluence.com    
Last modified: 1/15/18
